[♪ theme music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
You're already out.
-I'll see you around.
-[aunt] Sure.
Hey, did you say
the walking trail was that way?
-It is.
-Right.
What about your wife?
-Sorry?
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
His wife?
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
CACTUS
[automated message plays faintly]
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
[hesitates]
[♪ dramatic music continues]
[♪ comical sting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[♪ dramatic sting]
[♪ gripping dramatic music playing]
[Meri exclaims softly]
Does he know those people?
-In there--
-No way.
No.
No can do. I mean...
I want to check out the walking trail.
-Yes, but--
-But anyway.
Let's go.
Come along.
I want to check that out now.
[Sanghyeon] But...
-[Kim Wooju] Right away.
-[sighs]
[sucks teeth]
Oh, boy. [sighs]
Oh, this thing.
-Did he see it?
-No.
But it doesn't matter if he knows.
He'll hear about it from Grandma.
Still, do not say a word.
What if he puts a wrench in the works?
Well, yes. He could do that.
Wooju seems to have something like
an inferiority complex around me.
[laughs smugly] It's because I grew up
in a loving environment.
Did he say his friend lives here?
-Right?
-Yes.
Which friend?
-[GPS] It's 3:00 p.m.
-I don't know, and it's 3:00 p.m. now.
Okay.
MOM
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[car approaching]
Hey, wait. Stop the car.
[Eungsoo] What for?
Isn't this a ringtone?
-It's not mine.
-It's not mine, either.
There's a phone over there.
What? There's a phone out there?
-Yes.
-Here.
What? Why are you so nosy, Mom?
You be quiet.
-Mom.
-[phone continues ringing]
What's wrong with her?
That punk is so inconsiderate.
He should help people
get their things back.
Why are you so nosy?
-Seriously, why?
-Oh, dear. I missed the call.
Let's see.
Mom, we don't have time to...
-[♪ gripping whimsical music playing]
-There's no time.
What got into her this time?
You stay there.
-[♪ dramatic sting]
-[gasps]
[dog barks]
What are you doing?
[♪ unsettling, dramatic music playing]
-[chittering]
-[gasps]
[Eungsoo] What's that?
[Miyeon] Oh, my. Oh, my. Oh, my...
[Eungsoo] What's wrong with her?
Come here, Mom.
-Mom.
-Oh, my goodness...
-Oh, dear.
-Say you're sorry, Mom.
-[Miyeon] Wait, what is...
-[Eungsoo] Go on.
Hey.
Well, this...
Is this your phone?
It was on the ground, so I picked it up.
-Apologize, Mom.
-Is this...
-Give it to her already.
-Gosh.
-Sorry.
-Goodness.
-Oh, dear.
-[Meri] Thank you.
-I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
Oh, dear, she looked fine,
but she must be ill.
She seemed to be mentally unstable.
She doesn't seem to know
if she can talk or not, does she?
There's no way someone unstable
would live in this neighborhood.
-Is this place cursed or...
-[dog growls softly]
Oh, look at the doggy.
[gasps]
That thing looks unwell, too.
Hang on.
[barks] It won't react.
[barking]
This doesn't look good.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[growling]
[both panicking]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
EPISODE 3
I told the managing director
that you'd left home already.
Where did you hide earlier?
You disappeared in an instant.
[dog barking]
Just somewhere.
[chuckles softly]
He didn't catch on, did he?
No, fortunately.
-So, who were those people?
-They were my relatives.
[gasps]
It could've gone bad for us.
What did I tell you?
If you stay there,
you might meet more people you know.
[sighs]
Fine, I won't live there. Don't worry.
Did you find a place to stay?
You said you had to move out
of your old place.
Well...
I'll start looking.
Okay, all I ask of you
is that you sort things out,
so I don't have to worry
about you anymore.
Our deal is done here.
I know when I've overstayed my welcome.
I won't ask any more of you.
Then, goodbye.
Bye.
[line disconnects]
Goodness.
He's so mean and unkind.
But still,
he did me a great favor.
I have to pay back both Mom and the loan.
He's a lifesaver.
Yes, he saved my life.
She was short of breath
early in the morning.
And she feels dizzy more frequently.
That's because of her blood pressure.
Does she take her medication on time?
Yes.
I'm old, that's all.
Old bodies are bound to break down.
Ms. Kim, go check that for me.
Sure.
You need to reduce
your stress and workload.
And your sodium intake.
Okay, I will.
[chuckles softly]
Now that you're a real doctor,
you're nagging me like one.
[chuckles]
She's old enough to get married.
Do you have someone in mind as a suitor?
She had eyes only for one
since she was a kid.
Your grandson Wooju.
Dad.
You still like him?
Why won't you do anything?
You need to drop hints like crazy.
He won't know how you feel.
Do you approve of me?
I'd love for you
to be my granddaughter-in-law.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
I'll trust you've got my back
and make my move on him.
Yes, give it a go.
Director Yoon.
We might become in-laws.
How about we wrap it up this year
while we're at it?
[all chuckle]
MYUNGSOONDANG
[♪ soft, gentle music
playing over speakers]
Oh, Mr. Kim?
Hey. You came in early.
It's not yet time to clock in.
I'm the youngest on the team,
so I need to come in early.
And I love being at work.
[acknowledges]
What would you like?
-Is it your treat?
-Yes.
An iced Americano, then.
One iced Americano
and another one with two extra shots.
I'll pay for these as well.
-Okay, is it to go?
-Yes.
I'll treat you next time.
Promise to give me a chance.
Okay.
[Sejung] Hello, Mr. Jang.
Oh, hi, Sejung.
Go on your way. [in English] Good morning.
-Mr. Jang?
-[in Korean] Yes?
-What?
-A word?
Okay.
[mouthing]
[sighs] You heard, didn't you?
About what?
[laughs]
The contract.
[in English] You did a good job.
[in Korean] You punk. I knew you'd manage.
I believed in you all along, kid.
Okay?
[laughs loftily]
We can laugh about it.
Do you need anything
from the Business Management Team?
-Name it.
-Not doing anything
is the best you can do.
Focus on your own job.
You and the design company CEO...
Do you know each other?
[clears throat]
How would I know her?
I don't know anyone here.
True. You have zero contacts here.
What kind of deal did you offer
that made her sign it so easily?
Can you tell me that at least?
Are you upset I didn't get a bad deal?
[scoffs, hesitates]
Why would I be upset?
What kind of skills
does my dear cousin have?
I'd like to humbly learn
a few things if I could.
[chuckles softly]
I won't tell you.
Ask her yourself if you want to know.
I have to head to a meeting.
[stutters] I'm not done talking, punk.
I have a meeting, too, you know.
You...
How dare he?
I wish he would trip up
just a bit on the way.
[chuckling]
It worked.
I swear there's more to it.
You have something urgent to tell me?
Yes, well...
It's about J Consulting,
the company that's helping us
enter the US market.
Yes, is there an issue with them?
Could you take a look at this?
FINANCIAL STATEMENT
Other than the monthly consulting fee,
we wire J Consulting all the funds
to build the US factory
and pay the subcontractors as well.
It looks like J Consulting
is embezzling some of it.
[♪ gripping, tense music playing]
I found it odd
and contacted our US counterpart,
and the company itself seems to have
exaggerated their performance.
About this.
Mr. Ko, does anyone other than you
know of this?
No. Right now, it's just me.
You're the first person I'm alerting.
That's very wise of you.
Keep this confidential for now.
I'll look into it as soon as I can.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
REALTOR
[relator] I have a place
that will be available in a week.
Even if it's a short-term lease,
the deposit is five million won.
[sighs] I don't have five million won.
[sighs deeply] The dry sauna closed down,
and I have nowhere to go.
[inhales deeply]
My only friend who lives in Seoul...
is Gyeonghwa.
[line ringing]
[line connects]
Hey, Gyeonghwa.
How are you doing?
-What's up, Meri?
-[♪ whimsical music playing]
My place?
Oh, you should've called
just a tad sooner.
I moved out.
Why else? I joined the army.
Salute.
[chuckles] Man, you didn't know?
I enlisted last month.
Are you serious?
You mean you're an officer?
I wouldn't know if you don't tell me.
I didn't tell until I got in.
It would be embarrassing if I failed.
But why do you need a place
for three months?
I thought you got one before the wedding.
The schedule got a bit messed up.
There's a thing or two.
It can't be helped, then.
-Is something wrong?
-Oh, no.
I'll find some place else.
Hey, don't worry about me and eat well.
Look after yourself.
[chuckles softly]
Sure, salute to you, too.
[line disconnects]
Gosh, what should I do now?
[♪ enthralling music playing]
DAEJONG MOTEL
NO DEPOSIT, LONG-TERM STAY WELCOME
[♪ gripping music playing]
[siren wailing]
DAEJONG MOTEL
[couple chattering]
[woman] Why did we bother coming here?
-[man] Wait, I can--
-[woman] Let go of me.
[man] It was the alcohol, okay?
Sir, can't we get a refund?
-We were here just ten minutes.
-[receptionist] No.
-We don't need a refund.
-Let me go.
Give me another shot.
I can do it this time.
No, you couldn't even last a minute.
[man] I swear.
-Are you alone?
-Yes.
[sniffles]
You can't cook in the room.
If you have dirty clothes,
leave them with the cleaning lady.
-She'll charge you per kilo.
-Okay.
Good night.
[♪ dramatic sting]
[panting]
[grunts softly]
[continues panting]
[footsteps approaching]
[♪ gripping whimsical music playing]
[door handle rattling]
[sighs in relief]
[soft electrical hum]
[sighs wearily]
It's just for three months.
This place is a mess.
DO NOT BE WORRIED!
THE BEDDING HAS BEEN FRESHLY REPLACED
[♪ whimsical music playing]
DAEJONG MOTEL
[exclaims in disgust]
I doubt I can fall asleep here.
[phone alarm ringing]
ALARM
[phone alarm continues]
[alarm stops]
What time is it?
[♪ dramatic sting]
No way.
[♪ enthralling music playing]
My jacket.
Where is it?
[sighs] My phone.
The samples.
What's this in my hair?
Here you go.
It's the safest thing to give out
as an opening souvenir.
The transparent bottle
shows how much is left,
and the pump is gentle enough
for kids to use it.
The name of your clinic
and the logo are on the label.
Isn't the logo a bit too small?
I thought you'd say that,
so I prepared a sample with a bigger logo.
Do you want it to be bigger or not?
I think this will do.
Okay, then I'll confirm the design
and move ahead.
[doctor] Okay.
I'll see you next time.
-See you.
-[woman] Goodbye.
[hesitates]
Aren't you...
[exclaims in realization]
Hello.
Are you unwell?
No, I was here for work.
[acknowledges]
[♪ soft orchestral music playing
over speakers]
[footsteps approaching]
Thank you.
I dropped by
because a college friend opened a clinic.
-Today is my day off.
-I see.
Have you healed okay?
Oh, yes.
You treated me so well that time.
Thank you for that.
Not at all.
I should look out
for Wooju's acquaintances.
-Hmm.
-So, was that the first time you'd met?
Yes.
There was a slight mishap that time.
I said I was fine,
but he insisted on taking me
to see a doctor.
He paid for the treatment
and even took me home.
I was a huge nuisance.
He's known to be caring and polite.
He grumbles,
but does what he can to help out.
I see.
It looks like you kept contacting him.
He told me he saw you again,
and that you were a bit strange.
I was?
What on earth did he say to her?
He said something about you asking him
to be your husband.
What?
That fool.
Did he tell her everything?
We're really close, that's all.
There's nothing we don't know
about each other.
[chuckles nervously]
Don't mind that at all.
It was just a joke.
Don't we all joke like that
every now and then?
[♪ comical sting]
[chuckles]
It's just my neighborhood, then.
What?
Did he say anything else?
Like what?
Never mind.
MYUNGSOONDANG
Thank you.
He told me to watch myself.
We should sign a non-disclosure agreement.
What kind of guy
blabbers about everything?
MYUNGSOONDANG PACKAGING DESIGN PROPOSAL
As you can see,
Myungsoondang's packaging
is usually simple and generic.
So, on days other
than major national holidays,
they seem a bit old-fashioned
for exams, Christmas, or birthdays.
The new packaging
caters to various special occasions
other than just national holidays
with a more youthful, cute design.
I like it.
-That one over there is cute.
-They're pretty.
It would be a Stargram hit.
[remote beeps]
Thank you.
[all applauding]
I like it.
Wouldn't everyone want one?
What do you think?
It looks nice.
-[Sejung] I really like the colors.
-[whispers] Good job.
[Wonseok] This looks pretty cute.
-Thank you.
-Well done.
Mr. Kim.
You young people
have such great ideas and taste.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
[chuckles softly]
-Oh, Ms. Yoo.
-Yes?
Are you free this evening?
Well, yes.
-[♪ whimsical music playing]
-Are your glasses filled?
Okay, everyone.
To the collaboration
of Myungsoondang and Merry Design Studio.
-Cheers!
-[all] Cheers!
[exclaims]
Look at the marbling on the meat.
Prime beef surely is better.
Please enjoy, Mr. Kim.
Yes, thank you.
-You should eat, too, Sejung.
-I will. By the way...
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-I don't.
What about an ideal type?
[Kim Wooju] Not really.
Are you against marriage?
No, I'm not against marriage,
but I don't think it's a must, either.
[Wonseok] Hey.
You and I are on the same page.
I guess handsome guys think alike.
Wonseok, you're not in his league.
You're not single by choice.
-You applied to be on I Am Single.
-[scoffs]
-For real?
-I caught him
-filling in the application form.
-[chuckles softly]
You'll talk about anything.
When will you be on the show?
I heard the competition's fierce.
Wait, they didn't call for an interview?
-[bangs table]
-See? What did I tell you?
If you want to get married,
you must go all in and buy an apartment.
You still rent a place,
which is worse than losing hair.
I told you to buy
the old apartment in Ojun-dong.
It would've been great
if you'd bought it then.
The value increased by 50 million won.
[sighs]
Okay.
Let's drink.
Sure.
You can't afford a home
with a normal salary these days.
I've given up in this lifetime.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Why don't you enter
a department store raffle?
They give away five-million-dollar places.
[Wonseok] Five million dollars?
That's a thing?
[Ms. Oh] You didn't know?
Hang on. Is it over?
It was Beauté Department Store.
Beauté Department...
[♪ gripping dramatic music playing]
How about more beef? Korean beef.
-Korean beef?
-Yes.
Can you all eat some more?
Yes, of course.
[Ms. Oh exclaiming] Assorted special cuts?
Neck chain, tri-tip, inside skirt...
What do I do? Order them all?
It sounds so good.
Excuse me!
-Over here, ma'am.
-Yes?
I heard about that raffle, too,
but I think it's over.
They have announced the winner.
Oh, hang on.
Oh, Sejung.
-Let's have a drink.
-Oh, okay.
-Let's link arms.
-Us, you mean?
Us, I mean.
Hey, the winner was announced.
The winners are Seoul residents, Yoo...
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Jaein and Kim Minseok.
"They came to the store
to furnish their new home
and happened to enter..."
I'm jealous. [chuckles softly]
Wait.
Why do they look so familiar?
These people...
Ms. Oh, haven't we seen these people--
Overcooked beef never tastes as good.
Isn't it good?
Oh, it's hot.
Okay, everyone. If your glasses are empty,
I'll fill them for you.
-Yes, sounds good.
-Sure.
How about a group toast?
-Okay.
-[all] Cheers!
[cheering]
It's so good.
[sighs]
I'm drunk.
I can't be. I need to sober up.
I need [hiccups] to stay alert.
Ms. Yoo, are you all right?
-You drank a lot.
-Yes. [hiccups]
[slurring] I'm fine.
I like seeing this side of you.
You know I like people like you, right?
[giggles] Thank you.
[hiccups]
You're paying, aren't you?
-What?
-Our team leader's new to the job.
Show your appreciation.
Thanks for the Korean beef dinner.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[acknowledges]
I sobered up.
[digital beeps]
Oh, this card is overdrawn.
Oh, then...
Try this one.
Okay.
[digital beeps]
This one, too.
I paid the office rent yesterday.
Give me a moment.
-Sure.
-Another card...
My other card...
-Take your time.
-Okay.
-[Kim Wooju] Put it on this one.
-Sure.
I should pay for the dinner.
[Ms. Oh] Mr. Kim.
Ms. Yoo offered to pay today.
Why should someone from another company
pay for our dinner?
That's against company regulations.
But Ms. Yoo insisted she'd pay.
Thanks for the sentiment.
Wait, Mr. Kim.
The sentiment?
I never offered anything.
Excuse me? Mr. Kim!
I'll head home.
If anyone wants to stay out,
go have some fun.
Thank you.
[chuckles] Shall we go
to a karaoke, then?
-Deal!
Ms. Yoo.
-You should come, too.
-Me?
It looks like she had a lot to drink.
[exclaims] It's no fun without her.
-We're just getting started.
-Yes, let's go.
No, I think...
Where do you live? I'll drop you off.
I live near...
Get in.
-[♪ comical music playing]
-I'll get in.
Good. [chuckles nervously]
We'll be going then.
[Meri] Goodbye. Goodbye!
[chuckles softly]
[engine starts]
[Wonseok] Goodbye!
[Ms. Oh] What a shame.
I was going to make her pay for karaoke.
[groans softly]
Karaoke.
I wanted to go.
Wash your feet and go to bed.
I didn't want you to blurt anything out.
"Blurt anything out"?
He said something about you asking him
to be your husband.
[snorts]
You shouldn't go around saying things.
What?
I rarely make mistakes like that.
Didn't you see me
refraining from drinking?
You should be extra careful
when you're around others.
Don't get me worried, too.
You moved, right? Where is it?
Are you asleep?
Tell me where you live
before you doze off.
Goodness.
What the heck?
Gosh, how much did she drink?
DAEJONG MOTEL
[♪ comical music continues]
[grunts, panting]
Try to walk, will you?
-Which room is it?
-What?
-This is it.
-This is the one?
It's this room.
Thank you.
Sure. I'm off, then.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
[pants]
Where's my key card?
Oh, dear.
-It was in here.
-Did you leave it in the room?
[gasps]
What do I do?
-[sighs in exasperation]
-[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
Jeez, this is the fifth floor.
-I'll go downstairs.
-No.
-I'll go.
-No, no.
-Stay here. No, you stay.
-I can go.
No, stay here.
-I can--
-I prefer it this way.
Watch your arm. Wait here.
-Stay here.
-I can walk just fine.
No, it's better if you stay here.
-Here?
-Yes.
[Meri mumbles]
See you later.
Just wait right there.
[snoring]
[beeping]
You can go inside.
Oh, thank you.
She had a lot to drink.
[clears throat]
Go inside.
-[snoring]
-[Kim Wooju sighs]
[grunts]
Come along.
-Come here. Get up.
-I'm sleepy.
The door's open.
[receptionist] Be sure
to take your key with you.
[soft electrical hum]
Easy now. Careful.
[grunts]
[slurs] Thank you.
[panting]
[sighs]
[clears throat]
Oh, I found it on the floor outside.
[acknowledges]
Oh, sure. Thanks.
[♪ ominous sting]
[♪ tense music playing]
[gulps]
Do you have anything else to say?
Oh, no.
Have a good night.
[sighs in exasperation]
[sighs]
[gasps]
You're leaving already?
Yes.
Oh, right. Room 203 wanted more towels.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
Goodbye.
[♪ tense, gripping music playing]
[soft electrical hum]
[exclaims]
Easy now. Careful.
CACTUS
[line ringing]
Hi, Ms. Yoo. Is my car key in your--
[Meri screams]
Ms. Yoo?
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ music crescendos]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
BE BACK SOON
PLEASE WAIT
[panting]
What's going on?
[receptionist] Oh, you came back.
[Meri screams]
-Why--
-[Meri] Hold on.
Are you all right?
-[gasps] Oh, no.
-[receptionist] There's blood.
I'm bleeding.
[Meri] I'm sorry.
Why did you punch him like that?
What?
He was touching your legs...
[groans]
It wasn't like that.
I spilled my cup noodles
and burned my foot.
He came by with a first-aid kit.
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
I'm so sorry, sir.
-Oh, no.
-The blood won't stop.
-You're still bleeding.
-What a mess.
[receptionist crying]
[Meri] Let's try to stop it with this.
Well, I'm sorry.
[groans softly]
The rug needs cleaning,
so I docked it from your prepayment.
-Just so you know.
-Okay.
-I'm really sorry.
-[crying] Quit apologizing.
Jeez, I can't believe my rotten luck.
[continues crying]
-Let's go.
-Okay.
[receptionist] I think
I hurt my back, too.
[Meri] I can manage.
I didn't know you'd spilled something hot.
Who eats cup noodles
when they're half-asleep?
You had a huge dinner.
I was hungry.
I also wanted to eat beef,
but I didn't eat much because of the bill.
So, I was too hungry to sleep.
Sorry.
[♪ gentle music playing]
No, I'm sorry.
I'm not angry with you.
It's my circumstances that I can't stand.
Stay at a hotel.
Why scrimp when you'll soon
own a house worth millions?
Spend when you must.
I don't have the money
until the house is sold.
It's not sold yet.
I have an employee to pay
and a loan interest to cover.
I can barely afford the office rent--
[groans, sighs]
[♪ dreamy, ambient music playing]
[groans softly]
Shouldn't you see a doctor?
No, it's fine.
Thank you.
By the way, you pack a hefty punch.
Just one gave him a nosebleed.
[chuckles softly] That was nothing.
But do you really not have
a place to spend the night?
What about a friend or a relative?
I don't know anyone in Seoul.
It's fine. I'll just sleep
in my office for one night.
Give me that.
Where are we going?
Follow me.
[♪ feel-good music playing]
-Give it to me.
-Just go up.
Make sure he doesn't see you.
I will. I'll be as quiet as a mouse.
I'll go to work at dawn
and keep the lights off at night.
Okay.
Go on inside.
[whispers] Bye. Thank you.
[keypad beeping]
Thanks. Drive safely.
-[door closes, lock beeps]
-[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
Are you going home?
You've been working late.
The end of the quarter is always busy.
You should take a break afterward.
Of course.
My son's upset with me,
so I'll take him fishing next weekend.
[chuckling]
Sounds good.
Take this.
The chairwoman gave it to me,
but I had too many already.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
[elevator dings]
-Goodbye.
-Drive safely in the dark.
Yes, sir.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[sighs softly]
[engine starts]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
-[car horns blaring]
-[tires screech]
[groans]
What's wrong with me?
[clears throat]
[car horn blares]
-[tires screech]
-[truck horn blaring]
[screams]
[tires screeching]
[♪ gripping, tense music swells, fades]
[♪ soft, gentle music playing]
[sighs]
[♪ soft melodious pop music playing]
[yawns]
[sighs deeply]
[neck cracks]
[♪ gripping whimsical music playing]
Why won't he leave?
Gosh, that was close.
I should be careful.
-An interview?
-[Sanghyeon] I scheduled it
with an outlet to create an image
of connecting with young people.
Here is the list of questions.
Man, this game blows.
"I visited the couple that won the house
with a housewarming gift."
[scoffs] Who did?
I did? When?
You can drop by next weekend.
We need it for PR.
[sighs in exasperation]
You're such a nuisance.
Fine.
Hey.
Don't mess up this time.
-Pardon?
-We lost an entire house
because you messed up last time.
I'm giving you another shot.
Make up for it.
Yes, sir.
The CEO's visit?
It's an unofficial visit.
You don't have to worry.
[hesitates]
I need to discuss it with my husband.
Yes.
Okay, I understand.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Why does he want to visit?
[sighs wearily]
[gasps]
He didn't catch on, did he?
No, right?
What?
Mr. Ko?
He had been working late.
He must have dozed off behind the wheel.
[gasps softly]
Which funeral hall is it? Ready my car.
You'll go there now?
I should. He worked for us for years.
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
You're not well.
I'll go on my own today.
Go home and rest.
[breathing heavily]
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[Hangu] I don't know
what to say to console you.
Please stay strong.
Don't hesitate to contact me
if you need anything.
[sniffling]
[fitness instructor] Stand back up
and jog on the spot.
Shake your wrists. One, two.
Keep it light. Three, four.
Kick your feet back. One, two, three.
A bit faster now. One, two, three, four.
Someone's passing to our left.
Keep it up!
-Keep going.
[Sungwoo] Hey, Sanghyeon.
Don't mess up this time.
Your home, your car,
your credit card, your VIP membership.
I gave you all that to sort stuff out.
Make yourself worthwhile.
You can go now.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[faucet running]
[sighs]
Oh, my gosh.
How did people live
before they had electricity?
[screams]
My goodness.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[bottle cap clatters]
[sighs]
[car alarm chirps]
[hums softly]
[mosquito buzzing]
[exclaims softly]
A mosquito?
[persistent buzzing]
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[buzzing stops]
[buzzing resumes]
-[grunts]
-[buzzing stops]
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
[♪ tense whimsical music playing]
What's going on?
[♪ gripping, dramatic music playing]
[mumbles in frustration]
[sighs in exasperation]
[doorbell chimes]
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
[phone vibrating]
MANAGING DIRECTOR BAEK
[phone continues vibrating]
[Sanghyeon chuckles softly]
I had something to give you,
and you seemed to be home.
It's a parking permit form.
You haven't registered your car yet.
Thanks, I'll fill it in
and take it to the management office.
Do you know...
if I can ask the management office
to fix my lights?
Is there a problem?
The lights go on and off
on their own for no reason.
[exclaims in realization]
Did you activate the audio sensor?
Who, me?
-[gasps softly]
-[♪ enchanting music playing]
You can clap to control the lights
in the living room and each bedroom.
To deactivate the audio sensor...
[beeps] press "deactivate."
[exclaims in realization]
-Let's try it in the living room.
-Okay.
This is pretty useful when you're too lazy
to go upstairs to get the lights.
Press the button for the second floor
[beeps]
and clap.
You can control the upstairs lights, too.
I guess your husband isn't home yet.
Overtime.
Yes, he works overtime almost every day.
What does he do
if you don't mind me asking?
[hesitates]
He's an ordinary...
He works at an ordinary company.
[acknowledges]
[inhales sharply]
Does your husband actually live here?
-Yes, why?
-[♪ tense whimsical music playing]
I never see him around.
His car's not in the parking lot,
and I don't see his items
anywhere in the house.
The bedroom was full of your things.
And in the hallway, I only saw your shoes.
There's no trace of your husband.
It's as if you live apart.
So, my husband's...
His stuff is all upstairs.
We need to unpack, but we're too busy.
We should do that this weekend.
[chuckles nervously]
I see.
Yes.
[Meri chuckles]
Then I'll give you time to unpack.
Can our CEO visit next week?
Next week?
Next week...
[♪ jazz music playing over stereo]
-[phone vibrates]
-[clears throat]
[Meri] Do you have
any spare trainers or clothes?
What does this mean?
[music stops]
[line ringing]
Hello?
Well, I think I need to keep
some of your stuff at the house.
The CEO wants to visit.
What? The CEO?
I couldn't say no.
Mr. Baek was over, and he suspected us.
Mr. Baek was there?
What for?
[♪ whimsical music playing]
What?
Why did you try to kill the mosquito?
So what if you get bitten?
Would it kill you?
That's a matter of willpower.
When I was at Boy Scout camp,
I didn't complain
when I got bitten 20 times.
"I'll die if I get caught."
You should've put up with it.
Who can ignore a mosquito?
A fly, maybe.
Learn to put up with both.
You need to steel yourself
if you want to pull off a scam.
How will you manage
with a mindset like that?
Okay.
[clears throat]
When will the CEO visit?
Will you come?
[people chattering]
[both giggle]
[sighs]
[sniffles]
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
[♪ dreamy, ethereal music playing]
I didn't think
wedding photos would be necessary.
What newlywed couple
doesn't have one on the wall?
That's true, but...
I could also get into trouble
if you're caught.
[acknowledges]
Here.
[gasps softly]
They're plastic.
-I found them over there.
-[chuckles softly]
I see.
-Shall we begin?
-Yes, then...
Will you sit over there?
I'll stand next to you.
Okay.
[sighs]
[inhales sharply]
[exclaims]
None of the dresses fit me right.
I can barely breathe.
[clears throat]
-Excuse me.
-What?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Do you feel better?
Yes.
[Meri clears throat]
If we have to feel uneasy anyway,
we might as well do it properly.
A half-baked job will only get us caught.
[Meri acknowledges]
Then if you don't mind...
Move closer.
[soft, pulsing heartbeat]
[Meri] What's wrong with you, Meri?
Do you think these are
your actual wedding photos?
[Kim Wooju clears throat]
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
[camera timer beeping]
One, two, three.
I'm a bit puffy today.
-Hey.
-Face, check.
I'm extra cute today.
What am I going to do?
-Guys!
-Sejung's here.
Let's take some awesome photos today.
-Sounds good.
-How should we pose?
-What do you want?
-A sexy look?
-Okay.
-That's my specialty.
One, two, three.
-We're friends just for today.
-Perfect.
-Just for today.
[chuckling]
That was great.
-Good.
-Let's go.
[chuckles nervously]
I think that will do it.
[♪ dreamy, ambient music playing]
[exclaims softly]
Get changed. I'll see you outside.
Okay.
[door opens]
-[sighs softly]
-[door closes]
[sighs]
[Sejung's friend 1] Sejung,
did you bring those shades?
[Sejung] Yes,
shouldn't you come prepared?
You're such a thoughtful planner.
[♪ dramatic sting]
[♪ gripping whimsical music playing]
Mr. Kim?
[Sejung's friend 2] What?
I think I just saw someone I know.
[Sejung's friend 2] Who?
[Sejung] My team leader.
-Hang on.
-Why?
-What? We're going back in?
-Hurry.
Why?
-Out there...
-Yes?
Sejung's here.
What?
Where did he go?
Shouldn't you say hi?
I should, right?
Why would you do that?
Hey, is he good-looking?
Hey.
Hurry up, then. I want to meet him.
-Hello? Mr. Kim?
-Open all the rooms.
What now? What do we do?
-Let's...
-There's nowhere to hide.
Sorry for this.
[♪ dreamy, ambient music playing]
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Mr. Kim?
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
[Meri] Don't you know
offense is the best defense?
He was clearly suspicious last time.
[Sanghyeon] Unsolicited words of comfort
are just arrogance.
[Kim Wooju] Baek Sanghyeon?
[Hangu] Team Leader Kim?
[Kim Wooju] Why do you need to change?
You'll meet someone
who won't take your love for granted.
You liar.
My mom's in Seoul and heading to Wooju's.
[Wooju's mom] This isn't a lovers' spat.
It's over between them.
[Kim Wooju] Don't worry.
I think she's ready
to hear your side of the story.
[Wooju] Yoo Meri.
Kim Wooju.
Translated by Jennifer Jean Lim